NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE
FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
He is there!
Osman!
You are trapped just like a mouse!
Give me the one who killed my unarmed
soldier!
I want Göktuğ!
I know he is with you!
Flatyos…
… did your man die because of a tiny bite…
… or an incubus?
Tell me!
You are surrounded, Osman!
If you want to live, give me Göktuğ!
I took care of many dogs like you in the
past.
Now it’s your turn.
You are going to die!
You will die.
Bamsı Bey!
My sturdy Osman.
My Osman.
I did what you ordered, my Bey.
May you live long.
Osman will hide Göktuğ till we are safe
from Geyhatu’s terror.
With Allah’s permission…
… we will defeat Geyhatu when Savcı
becomes victorious.
With Allah’s permission, my Bey.
With Allah’s permission.
What’s wrong, Abdurrahman?
My Bey…
I said what’s wrong.
… Osman Bey.
What about him?
Osman...
… as if the ground split and he entered
the ground.
I hope he listens to what I said…
… and that he is not after his brother,
Savcı.
Osman...
… I hope he won’t make such mistakes.
My son.
My Bamsı Bey.
-Allah is eternal!
-Allah is rightful!
You will pay for this, Osman.
My Bamsı Bey.
Oh, my lion!
Oh, my sturdy Osman!
As if Allah sent you here.
Where did you come here?
Always look for the savior.
Sturdy Osman, Ertugrul Gazi’s son!
I see you are fighting against yet
another trouble.
Where have you been?
We missed you so much.
I will tell you where, once we are at
the Tent.
Come on, son.
My mission is very important.
My Savcı brother needs me, Bamsı Bey.
Abruhhaman Gazi told me about everything.
However, my Osman, please don’t.
So that you and your father will be on
good terms.
Let’s go, my son.
Send him my regards.
I put a man on my brother’s tail.
And I will find where he is.
Now, I have to go against my father’s
orders.
Finding Möngke is the only way to stop
Geyhatu.
Even if your father tells you to stop,
son?
I know it will have bad consequences.
And that, nothing will be the same
between me and my father.
However, the mad horse inside me tells
me to go on.
It tells me to find my brother!
Son...
… is it really the mad horse inside you…
… or is it your honour?
Don’t you believe me, Bamsı Bey?
My sturdy Osman…
… I’m only scared.
I’m only scared…
… because you are walking on Al-Sirat.
Many Valiants and Heroes…
… we lost…
…as the results of such games of Devil.
The dream of becoming a hero killed many
Valiants of ours.
So, tell me son, are you faltering in the
very same dream?
If I ever go against my father’s words
and follow my honour…
… I shall be reaped inside out and
chopped by swords.
If you say so..
… so be it then (Eiwallah).
So be it.
May Allah be with you, from now on.
My Bamsı Bey.
If I don’t make it back to Tent…
… tell my father…
… to give his blessings.
Tell him to forgive me.
You did a good job, Möngke.
A very good job, indeed.
You are my beloved, Möngke.
Of course I shall be your beloved.
I gave you Kayıs and you will give me
father’s flesh.
You will relieve his anger by pretending
to save me.
You will save Kayıs from a huge massacre.
You will shine like a star before the
eyes of Turks.
You are the one who will benefit the most
from this, Möngke.
Your father’s grave will be at Söğüt…
… and you will replace him.
How are you going to kill him?
Your conscience will hurt if I tell you
so.
I tied a rock to my conscience and threw
into Caspian Sea.
I tell my plans to no one.
The ground may have ears.
You just keep dreaming of the crown you
will take.
Who knows, maybe you will become the Khan
of Mongols once you replace your father.
Genghis Khan is my ancestor.
Khanship is my birth right.
And you are my friend for life.
Once I establish my own state...
… try not to be an enemy but a friend.
I have to go now.
In the meantime, you shall learn how
Savcı found about this place.
And that if someone else knows too.
Do the things I tell you so that our
heads will stay on their place.
Fool…
… eventually, your turn will come.
Take them away!
Once you kill my father, it will be your
turn.
Brother, what if something happened to
our Bey?
You two are Alps who act like sad owls.
Our Bey has been away for too long,
Kumral Abdal.
Do you like your Bey so much?
More than our own lives.
I would believe you if I didn’t see the
things I saw.
Do we have flaws, Kumral Abdal?
No human is flawless!
It's worse than that.
Please, we are already troubled,
Kumbral Abdal.
Tell us already if we have any flaws.
So that we can change for good.
We wouldn’t like to be bashful for our
Bey.
Your heart and your tongue act the
opposite way.
You know what they tell about such people.
May Allah never allow that.
Since when we are heathens?
There are some who say they believe…
… but they never surrender to Allah.
Don’t you ever become one of them.
He who loves, never gets sad or worried.
At once, reach to the level of those who
surrendered!
How can we reach to that level?
I know but I won’t tell you.
After all, you are already in the
melting pot.
Perhaps, you will find out yourself.
You need to be burned and cooked
for a while.
Hand this to your Bey.
I will go now.
My mission is completed.
Kumral Abdal!
Where are you going?
My Rab, may you protect our reason.
Our level is not a level at all, brother.
If we continue like this, we may end up
in hell.
May Allah never allow that, brother.
May we pledge.
Selâmün aleyküm.
Aleyküm selam, my Bey.
I hope you are okay, Göktuğ.
Thanks to Allah, my Bey.
Thanks to Allah.
I’m standing here, thanks to Abdurrahman
Gazi.
I knew it.
I knew it!
My Valiant father.
My lifeblood father.
Kumral Abdal gave this, my Bey.
What’s that, my Bey?
Our guide to Devil’s pit.
Let’s go.
My brother is waiting for us.
I hope it's for the good.
You are taking away your goods from
the shelf.
What else can I do, Davut brother?
Our Tent is not the same as it was.
We didn’t even make the first sale of
the day.
I will try my luck somewhere else.
Patience.
We are going through hard days.
You can’t surrender like this.
We are always struggling with something.
When will we able to feed ourselves?
Where are you thinking of going?
No idea, Davut brother.
They say, there is business in Yalvak
Arslan’s Tent.
I will try there.
You coward!
You are running away because of hardships!
Look at me!
You can’t achieve anything without
struggling!
If you ever try to run away, I’ll burn
you alive!
Okay, I get it, Davut Brother.
Is your strength only enough for wretched
ones like me?
You only want to choose the easy way.
Don’t.
Now, put the goods back on the shelf.
I’m ready to die for you.
Thank you, blacksmith!
Welcome!
Welcome, my Bey.
Thank you.
Know that I won’t greet anyone before I
greet my Bey.
He is inside, my Bey.
Do I have your excuse, my Bey?
Come in.
Where does the path lead?
To the Red Apple.
For what cause?
For Shahada.
Oh, look at my mighty Valiant!
My Bey!
My dear Bey!
I’ve been waiting for this moment for
too long.
Now that these eyes are on your presence…
… may my Rab, take my remaining years and
give them to you.
May my Rab never separate us, even in
the after life.
Amin.
-Amin.
-With Allah's permission.
Okay…
… your Bamsı Beyrek is all good.
He is very good indeed.
What’s the situation with escrows?
Anything…
… everything is under control.
Don't you worry, my Bey.
When the time comes, everything will be
revealed.
Then, with Allah’s permission, the sun
will rise again.
Our state will stand straight once again.
With Allah’s permission, my Bey.
Tell me, Bamsı.
Don’t tire out yourself.
I know my Bey.
I know where your Osman is.
So do I.
He told me he has a man on Savcı’s tail.
He knows where he is.
He says he won’t come back to Tent unless
he finds his brother.
My Bey...
... didn’t he do the right thing by
following his brother?
Let me be your sacrifice.
At least, you tell me something about it.
He may pretty much support his Savcı
brother.
He didn't listen to my words.
I grabbed his hand and took him to
the Tent...
... yet again he didn't listen.
He doesn't listen to his father's,
his Bey's words.
Then what is necessary
has to be done!
It’s time to make harsh
decisions about Osman.
If he’s like this while I’m alive,
I don’t know what he’ll do…
… to follow what he thinks is the truth.
My Bey. Osman went too far. I know.
But he has good intentions.
The road to hell is filled with
stones of kindness.
What would you do if you were
worried about Gündoğdu Bey?
You also know that my
Osman loves his brothers.
He went because he loves his brother.
Not because he wants to disobey you.
Osman is just one of my Beys.
If every one of my Beys follows their own
truth, what will this Tent’s future be?
Do you ever think of that? We’ll
put the tent in order immediately.
- I’m here for your orders, my Bey.
- Thank you.
We’ll build a defence line.
The sands are running out.
We don’t know what
that dog Geyhatu will do.
You’re in charge of the defence line.
Start the preparations.
Thank you, my Bey!
Why are you smiling?
Are you pleased with yourself?
- I understand the situation now.
- What is it?
You blamed Osman and made your escape.
How did you find where I was hiding?
What is such a trick’s intention anyway?
What were you expecting to happen
after you blamed Osman?
Your father would be angry and
come to Söğüt with his army.
How did you find this place, I asked!
Okay. How do you benefit from this?
Answer my question? How did you trace me?
Does anyone else know?
Are you afraid your father
will hear about it, Möngke?
You’re afraid of your father
as much as you hate him, correct?
Someone is going to kill
your father in Söğüt, correct?
You were going to get your father
killed and blame Osman for it, correct?
How did you find this place? Talk!
You’re a smart man. You know
what will happen if you don’t talk.
You will kill me whether I talk or not.
But I have one with before I die.
Give me the name of that
dog who collaborated with you.
Tie him up to the bone breaker.
His death will be painful.
I’m sick of this place anyways.
And I’m not in a hurry.
You’re all in the herbs again, Lena.
Thank you. Habits of my mother.
It’s my first time seeing this one.
It’s a cure for everything.
I’ll make a new medicine from it.
And maybe it will help you have a child.
Do you think it will be?
Of course it will!
Every herb has a language. If you can
figure it out, you’ll get its benefits.
Inshallah!
Any news from Osman Bey lately?
He set off with his horse after
hearing what happened to Göktuğ.
Ertuğrul Bey won’t allow something
to happen to Göktuğ. Don’t worry.
Osman Bey also knows this.
Yes. But that tyrant called Vladius
won’t let go of the situation.
Have you heard of this name?
Hazal Hatun!
What’s the situation?
I found it while cleaning
Ertuğrul Bey’s tent.
So, the old bird will soon fly away.
Be ready, brother!
I hope Osman Bey and Savcı Bey
will return safe and sound.
I hope Osman Bey didn’t
disobey his father.
Hatuns! Have you heard of what happened?
What is it, Hazal Hatun?
Did you hear something?
Or did Bamsı Bey bring any news?
Göktuğ escaped the dungeon.
What are you saying, Hazal Hatun?
Everyone’s saying that Osman did it.
As if all of our troubles
weren’t enough, now this!
Osman Bey doesn’t disobey
his father, Hazal Hatun!
Something fishy is going on.
My Bala! Everything is obvious.
Besides, there’s more.
Osman Bey disappeared with his alp Boran.
So, Bala Hatun? You couldn’t
get a hold of your man.
What will happen now?
Ertuğrul Bey is dealing with Osman’s
madness in the middle of everything!
Enough, Hazal Hatun!
If Osman Bey is doing something,
he has a reason for it!
Bala! I warned you countless
times as your elder!
A Hatun disciplines her man, I said.
But instead of disciplining your man,
you’re attacking us with your words!
I trusted and believed you. But I see
that the devil captured your heart!
And your tongue became the devil’s tongue!
Bala! Do something about your words or--
Or what?!
Or I know how to tear it off.
Try it if you’re brave enough!
See what happens to you!
I called you my bride, my daughter.
You fell from my grace, Bala.
You’ll learn what that means
but it will be too late.
My Bey! Their lair Kumral Abdal was
talking about must be this way!
Then we will destroy that lair!
- Will we infiltrate it, my Bey?
- We will hit it.
We’ll destroy everything! Let’s go!
Bala Hatun won’t be able
to give Osman Bey a child!
Pity! How can a man like
Osman Bey be without a child?
They’re a looking for a new Hatun for him.
I wouldn’t wish it on my worst enemy!
How can Osman Bey be without a child?
Hatuns! They’re looking
for a Hatun for Osman Bey.
Since Bala Hatun can’t have children!
It’s the right thing! Osman
Bey is our Tent’s future!
If he doesn’t have children,
he won’t be sitting on that throne!
And Lena Hatun is pregnant again.
Excuse me.
You’ll see what it means
to threaten me, Bala.
This Tent will be your hell.
You look sad, Bala.
How can I not be? Everything’s on fire.
As if dealing with
our enemies wasn’t enough.
We’re dealing with the devils among us.
Hazal Hatun again?
I thought she was innocent.
She’s trying to cause chaos
by breaking my bond with Lena Hatun.
She came to this Tent for a reason, Gonca.
There’s definitely a reason. We will see.
May Allah protect us.
- Good luck, Hatuns!
- Thank you.
Bala Hatun. We’ve heard that
Osman Bey was looking for a new Hatun.
Why would that be, Hatun?
Because you couldn’t get pregnant.
Take care of yourself. There’s a doctor
in Sivrihisar. You should see him.
Everyone knows about it now, my lady.
Good job, my beautiful daughter.
She made everyone talk about me.
Osman will also hear about it.
He will be embarrassed because of me.
Bala! Don’t give up that easily!
We’ll find a way.
It doesn’t matter, Gonca!
I’m thinking about Osman. He has dreams.
I don’t want those dreams
to be dreams because of me.
My Bala! What can you do
other than look for solutions?
I’ll sacrifice myself for Osman Bey.
What those that even mean, Bala?
Don’t say that!
We give our lives up for
other’s lives, Gonca!
Osman is this Tent’s hope.
Every Turkman’s hope.
...to keep that hope alive...
...I can even
marry Osman myself.
We have little more to go, my bey.
The preparations are done.
-Then, may Allah bless our holy war.
-My bey, what if we return empty-handed?
What if Savcı Bey had solved everything?
It's possible. But something inside me
don't let me wait.
Let's set off.
What will happen when you replace
your father?
So, you finally came round.
What will happen?
Will you kill Argun Khan like you
will kill your father?
My father will do it for me.
Well, well. What a loving family.
So, you will be the Mongol Khagan?
You will get everything without deserving.
Now, you better start speaking. Your suffering
will end. You will get a swift and sweet death.
I won't give you this pleasure.
We'll see.
A bear-like man came out of the forest,
Nicola. He took Osman.
Say that again.
Just when we hunted Osman, a bear
got him from us.
Tell me that again. Tell me that again!
Again!
A bear saved Osman.
A bear? A bear! A bear!
And you? Couldn't you show them
who the real bear is?
I want to drink blood, not wine.
Blood! Blood!
I will get such revenge from Ertuğrul that
I'll rip his heart. His heart!
Let's make them puke blood, Nicola.
What's in your mind, Nicola?
We'll go after Ertuğrul's other son,
like a nightmare.
A nightmare.
Ertuğrul...
There will be ditches dug on the
entrances of the fort.
And you will build steel stakes for
those traps.
This should be done before night.
Are we in that much danger, my bey?
We think that Nikola will attack by
taking the opportunity
I want you to take the best Alps and
masons with you...
...and close every hole you find
on the walls.
As you command, my bey.
I want the locks of the storehouses to
be changed too.
We can even change the doors
if you want, my bey.
Good. Now I'm going to take the taxes to Söğüt.
This will all be done before I return,
all right?
All right, my bey.
Mashallah, mashallah.
Thank Allah, this year was plentiful.
Come on Alps, Come on.
Intruders!
Osman...
How did he find here?
Your death has come, Möngke.
Go and check them out.
Welcome, my bey. Welcome, my bey.
Welcome, welcome, my bey.
Gündüz Bey.
Nikola.
As you see, I'm unarmed.
As my soldier that you killed.
What do you want, Nikola?
Justice.
My bey!
Gündüz Bey.
You will pay the price of breaking
the agreement.
Breaking it? Gündüz Bey, I came here
to get my right. An eye for an eye.
In return of my dead soldier.
I'll take a piece from Ertuğrul.
Brother.
Brother. Brother. Brother.
Please, open your eyes.
-Brother. -Brother.
-Möngke deceived us all.
-How did you get it.
You were both prisoners.
You were beaten up good, brother.
But he was fine.
Pretty fine.
If I was as vigilant as you,
I wouldn't be here.
Brother.
Without you, we wouldn't be able
to do this.
Without you, I wouldn't be alive. It's a
good thing that you didn't listen to me.
But...
...be afraid of Bala.
I'd give my life for both of you.
My lion brother.
Brother, we don't have much time.
But don't worry. You won't die.
But you will suffer.
My unarmed soldier was killed.
You killed my unarmed soldier...
...in front of hundred of your soldiers,
despite our agreement.
Tell your bey, if I see Osman or Göktuğ,
I will kill them.
He either brings them and trials them.
Or I will get things right. Tell your bey.
I won't be the one breaking the deal.
But if you break it, I'll make you pay.
My bey! My bey!
Gündüz Bey, I like to make people pay.
My bey. My bey.
I've been waiting for this for
a long time.
What if Savcı brings Möngke,
our holy leader?
Then we will declare war because their
horses neigh!
It's a small Turkmen tribe.
They aren't even worth your trouble.
-Why is this, sir?
-I wanted him to clean my honor first...
...but now the existence of Ertuğrul
blurs my mind.
It disturbs me.
Osman is a roaring lion.
We should crush his head...
...while he is little.
We found this spy prying on us.
Why did you bring him to me and
not just kill?
Your weapon can't kill me.
Kill this man, Cerkutay.
His bones will feed dogs.
Do it yourself if you can.
Your weapon doesn't have
the power to kill me.
Who the hell are you?
I'm a madman.
What were you looking for here?
I lost my army, I was looking for it.
Who is the commander of your army?
I am. Didn't you like that?
Where is your weapon?
Where are your soldiers?
They'll be here soon.
-What's the matter with you?
-I came to warn you.
-Go on your way.
-What if I don't?
Will you stop me?
Then, what happened to
Ebrehe's army will happen to you.
-Who the hell is Ebrehe?
-The tyrant who attacked the mother of cities.
-Tell me.
-I'll tell you when the time comes.
-Now, I'm warning you.
-Enough, you worthless.
You are wasting my time.
Time isn't yours!
Birds...
Ahmet!
What happened in your dream?
That tyrant.
-That cruel man was going to come to our tents-
-Which cruel man, Ahmed?
Geyhatu.
That cruel man which you call Geyhatu.
There is wisdom in dreams, Ahmed.
Tell me what you seen.
A man came up.
A dervish-like man.
With his staff in his hand.
He stood against the cruel man,
he ruined his house.
Birds, stones, winds...
They couldn't even use their swords.
They were all damned.
Inshallah your dream will come true
and we will beat the cruel.
Osman Bey will stop him.
Don't worry.
I know, Bala Hatun. I'm not worried.
Osman Bey is a roaring lion.
-Dumrul, you've been a comrade.
-I'd give my life to you, my bey.
Thank you.
I'm glad you came, brother.
It would be terrible without you.
Thank Allah for sending me, brother.
It was our duty.
Your duty was not coming.
But...
I'm glad you didn't listen to us.
It would be terrible without you.
Tell your inner voice, we
owe it a life.
Are our lives truly ours, brother?
But, for the first time, we
are in such a big scheme.
You see, even a son is planning
behind his father.
Who do you think is
behind this?
Someone must be holding the leash
of this dog. He can't do it alone.
I suspect Yavlak Arslan.
What are you saying, brother?
This is a heavy accusation.
If we can make him talk before
going to his father, we may find it.
Come on, my valiants!
Today is the day of honor!
Today, there is no surrender!
Today, there is no subjugation!
Today, there is no conceding!
Come on, valiants!
Be united!
Be a roaring lion!
Mashallah!
Mashallah, Bamsı Bey. You brought
life to our tents.
Thank you, thank you, Dündar Bey.
Now that I saw Ertuğrul Bey,
I'm as fresh as daisy.
The lion inside me roared.
These wrists of mine got stronger.
Mashallah, mashallah.
The reinforcements must've reached
Söğüt.
Mashallah, mashallah. Let's see.
Come on, valiants. We take measures,
but it's upt o Allah.
If Allah doesn't want to protect us,
great mountains can't protect us.
But if Allah...
...if Allah wants to protect us...
Even a spider web can be an armor
for us.
My Allah...
...protect us, my Allah.
-Amin.
Protect us and our tents from
the enemy, my Allah!
-Amin.
Come on, warriors. Come on, alps.
Come on, valiants.
Today is the day of honor.
Come on.
My bey, you should take a breath.
What is it? Did you think that I'm a
hoar like you, Abdurrahman Ghazi?
Not at all, my bey.
I just didn't want you to get tired.
Neither enemies nor traitors
tired me all these years.
What tires me, what bothers me...
...is what will happen after me.
As the father, who will I make me heir?
It's a great responsibility, Ghazi.
A great responsibility.
Gündüz, Savcı and Osman.
Three gallants of mine. Even if a single
gets sad about it...
...I'll be sad.
If they get hurt,
my heart will hurt.
I might stand like that but I'm a father.
My bey, my bey. My bey, incoming!
Clear the way! Clear!
-May it be good, Dündar Bey.
-May it be good.
-Gündüz? Gündüz! Gündüz!
-Gündüz Bey!
-Gündüz, tell me who did this to you?
-Gündüz, who did this treachery?
Nikola ambushed us, my bey.
We have wounded alps.
Come on, carry him to the tent.
Hold here. Hold here, valiants.
Return to your jobs.
-Gündüz.
-Everyone, return to your jobs.
There is no break.
There is no crying.
Today is the day of honor.
Everyone, return to your jobs.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Gündüz, my child.
Who did this to you?
Nikola, father, Nikola.
Gündüz...
Gündüz, my child.
Father, don't worry.
I'll cure my Gündüz brother.
Come on, Alps. Let's take him in.
-Alps, come on!
-Come on! Come on!
Come on!
He is taking revenge.
I will make him regret!
Once we get rid of this Geyhatu trouble.
I will make him regr...
My Bey!
If Kayıs can save so much gold
in this short time...
it means that they will grow.
Vladius, we need to get in action.
You are right, Nikola.
What are we going to do with gold?
I like being generous.
Let's give it to our people.
So that they believe in victory more.
Yavlak Arslan from Çobanoğulları has come.
Let him.
If you are planning an attack to
Kayıs and Turkmens...
taking advantage of their action with
Geyhatu's army.
Yavlak.
Is Osman included in what you are talking
about?
Osman.
What Osman?
Yavlak.
Stop acting like you don't know what
he has done.
You also know that neither you nor I
can peace as long as Osman lives.
Finally, a wise man
in the throne of enemy.
You couldn't protect even in my dream.
The ground swallowed him up.
We can't find Osman and Savcı.
Send your men to everywhere!
Everywhere!
Osman...
I will bury him alive.
Who did you collaborated with?
Talk, dog!
You are in hurry for your death!
Talk, you dog!
Talk!
You can't get a word from me.
My father will bury you all alive.
The secret has been revealed.
Tell me.
I saw, I went, as you said.
I am back with heavy news, son of a Bey.
May it be good. Tell us what you have.
Osman conquered one of our biggest castles
in his father's absence.
He humiliated two great Mongol unities
with their commanders.
I can't imagine what this young man would
do after his father's death.
What do you think, Yavlak?
Osman...
Who is Osman while Dündar is there.
Even you don't believe in what you say.
Osman would have ten men like Dündar
in pocket.
Neither Dündar nor his brothers can stop
him after his father dies.
Cool.
What interests you?
Osman is the biggest threat for me.
I am the biggest threat for you, Nikola.
If you're planning an attack to Kayıs, taking
advantage of....
their action with Geyhatu's army.
I swear that I will bury you in this
castle's rusty stones.
Don't worry.
Yavlak Arslan.
I am not intended to bother you as long as
Osman doesn't bother me.
- What is this?
- A gift. I like it.
I wanted our friendship to improve.
Nikola... you don't know about roosters
at all.
But I liked you.
You are kind.
I will see you again.
Me too, Yavlak.
Me too.
His wounds are heavy.
My Lord, grant us with him.
Bala bring some more balm.
- Bring, bring, bring.
- Take it.
He is unconscious.
He lost so much blood.
Gündüz Bey's arm seems really bad, Lena.
He won't be able to hold sword a while.
Lena, what's his situation?
He will be alright, my Bey.
Heal him, my daughter.
Don't worry, father. My treacle water
heal him up soon.
Bala, let's preapre some more balm.
I am Suleiman Shah's son Ertuğrul Ghazi.
I swear on my flag.
I will dig out the ones who did this
to you with my dark dagger.
I swear on my blood.
I will torment the ones who did this
to you like they are in hell.
Father.
My Father.
You shall sleep, my Gündüz.
My sunshine.
My child.
Inshaallah, you stand up
as soon as possible.
As soon as possible, my father.
Don't worry.
We have a valiant brother who didn't
buckle under cruelty.
May our holy war be blessed to stop
the cruels!
Eyvallah, my Bey.
You have a plan, we are sticking to it.
Let's see what happens, brother.
- Let's go now.
- Bismillah.
Ya Allah!
I am here to help you in your rough day,
Ertuğrul Bey.
What is it?
Do you have an army for me, Arslan?
- I came to stop Geyhatu.
- Only my sons can stop Geyhatu, Arslan.
I visited Nikola.
I warned him to not set his eyes on your
castles while Geyhatu is here.
Cruel dog!
He backstabbed me in my rough day!
I will make him regret!
I will take many lives for the blood
of Gündüz and Alps...
My Bey...
My Bey, my Bey...
My Ertuğrul Bey...
My Bey, my Bey.
Alps!
So, Geyhatu's son
Mongke was involved in this case.
Osman was just a bait in this game.
My closest Alps will save Mongke and bring
him here before Geyhatu attacks the tribe.
You'll save Kayıs from two big trouble.
From both Geyhatu and Osman.
I see both of them as an obstacle against
the state I will establish.
Geyhatu with his power, Osman with
his stubborness, they hamper me.
But today I will get rid of both of them.
Why don't you smile?
Ertuğrul Bey's death is not far. Osman is
the biggest trouble, we both know that.
But that Mongke, why is Mongke in this,
brother?
There's still a secret that you didn't
tell me about.
You have always been wise, my sister.
Brother, tell me for Allah's sake, what
will Geyhatu's son Mongke get?
Geyhatu will die today.
His son Mongke will take his place.
Osman will be his killer, and I will
establish the state.
What about Osman?
What if he pops up?
I thought everything.
I set a trap in their way.
- Let's see what happens.
- The Auburn Abdal did a good work.
They will be in the dark jungle.
Brothers.
The mission is yours.
I don't know who is in behind this, but
it will be revealed when this is over.
Let's go, valiants. Don't waste time.
His fever is going up, bring cold water.
Don't be hopeless.
Geyhatu can arrive anytime.
We are always prepared.
Just because our Bey is lying back there,
we won't be oppressed.
We won't let anyone dirty our honor.
Talk, Dündar Bey.
Everyone gathered, they are worried about
our Bey's condition.
As his brother, this is your mission.
People are worried about their life
and their Bey. Console them.
Kayı's vailant Hatuns, valiant Men,
valiant children!
I know you love for Ertuğrul Bey, and
I also know that...
you are in a deep sorrow.
However, it is true.
Our Bey's disease reappeared.
My Allah, don't let us be rudderless.
Our Bey will be healthy
soon, Inshaallah...
with Allah's permission.
Inshaallah!
Now, you should worry about
our tribe's future...
not his health.
Mongols...
are about to come.
You're all armed, all of you.
When the war is this close, we
should all be like...
Ertuğrul Bey.
Each of you will become Ertuğrul Bey.
So that we can deserve...
this beautiful land.
It doesn't matter who the enemy is..
what we should do is...
to follow our Bey!
Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest.)
My Bey, Geyhatu is here.
Come on!
Everyone, go fight!
Do your duty, come on.
Are there any news from
Kulucahisar and Karacahisar?
What's new?
Nikola.
Geyhatu is in Kızıltepe with his army.
Good.
What about our castles?
Our spies are waiting for your order to
take action in both of the castles.
I like action.
When Ertuğrul's men and
Geyhatu's army start to fight...
we'll go into action from three areas.
Commander, you go Kulucahisar.
Commander Nikis, you go Karacahisar and
you'll attack at the same time.
And I'll support you with my own unity.
What about Geyhatu?
The Mongols are the real owners of
Ertuğrul's lands.
How will we prevent Geyhatu's reaction?
When Geyhatu takes action with his army..
the only place that Turks can go is
Byzantine lands.
Commander Nikis.
Vladius will kill who runs away.
I'm sure Geyhatu...
will be grateful.
What about Yavlak Arslan?
Yavlak Arslan.
If he attacks...
killing him is...
my job.
As Caesar said...
"I came."
"I saw!"
"I conquered!"
"I came; I saw; I conquered!"
What will we do now?
The Mongol army.
How will we handle them?
We'll fight, İdris Efendi.
If we die, we die with honor.
That's good news.
What does it mean, my Bey?
Geyhatu wants to talk before the fight.
He obviously wants his son.
We don't know about his son.
We don't even have his dead body...
what are you saying?
I'll talk to him one last time.
Whatever happens.
Arslan Bey, you're not the
Bey of our tribe.
- This is our job.
- I'm not the Bey of the tribe, yes...
but I'm the Bey of Beys of this land.
Know your place, Bamsı Bey.
No need to talk.
Geyhatu wreaks his anger on us when
he doesn't see his son.
Arslan Bey is right.
We need to have time
until Savcı and Osman come.
Then...
the words are over and weapons will talk.
What are you doing here, Yavlak Arslan?
I want to talk about the problem
without having a fight.
It's none of your business, Yavlak Arslan.
I don't have time to talk.
I came here to take my son back...
and if I don't...
I'll kill Kayıs.
Helen.
Take this and go to the kitchen.
I'll come after you
Father.
Helen is here.
I need to learn where she is going.
Our spies are waiting for your order to
take action in both of the castles.
I like action. When Ertuğrul's men and
Geyhatu's army start to fight...
we'll go into action from three areas.
In and outs to the castle are banned.
The bazaar will be closed.
Go back to your work.
It'll happen during the change of shifts.
We have to be sure about
how many are they, Nikola.
Helen.
You came just on time.
Why is that privacy?
There's a spy in our castle.
He told where our
ammunition is to the Kayıs before.
Until we find him and...
hang him by the neck
on the edge of the walls...
we need to be careful.
Savcı, he is as troubled as Osman.
Helen, what is going on in Kulucahisar?
Here are the places for the watch.
There are twenty Alps on the walls.
They're changing shifts three
times during the day.
Are all the archers informed?
As you ordered...
the guard Alps will be poisoned before the
attack and they won't be able to fight.
What about the secret passage, Helen?
You and your soldiers go into
the secret passage from here.
And I'll open the door for you.
They won't have time to use their swords.
When Kayıs handle with Geyhatu, we'll
take our Kulucahisar back.
Don't you have a place for
the Roman Emperor?
Roma is little.
Mongols are big.
You'll wait standing.
Roma is big, Geyhatu.
Big.
You can't handle...
lots of Turkmen.
Wait standing.
Do you know why I summon you?
It must be something important, Geyhatu.
Important or not.
You'll come when I summon you.
Important or not, Geyhatu.
Why did you summon me?
I'm going to...
the Kayı tribe.
I will kill...
Ertuğrul and his daughters.
And you will...
get Kulucahisar back.
That's an important thing.
I like important news.
You look for a place to sit.
Go sit in Kulucahisar.
I will.
Come on.
Go.
Victory will be ours.
Victory is ours!
Savcı said...
he'd bring me my son.
Where is Savcı?
Where is my son?
Where is Osman...
the filthy Turk?
Geyhatu.
Let's talk in the tent.
If you say one more word...
I'll kill you first, Yavlak.
We sent my nephew to you as an envoy.
Don't you trust our words?
Osman abducted my son.
My nephew Osman doesn't
abduct his enemies.
He kills them.
If he's innocent, then where is he?
He should come!
He went after Savcı.
Savcı said he'd bring...
my son in three days!
Three days...
is when the sun goes down.
I'll kill all of the Turks on these lands!
Geyhatu...
if you want war, let's fight.
Maybe you wreck our tribe...
you kill us or maybe...
you take our heads off and go, but...
it won't be easy.
You'll be buried in a grave...
with your dignity and with us.
It's a good way...
to die, Geyhatu.
However...
we don't know who the
death will take first.
Don't, Geyhatu. Even if
Osman has done it...
Kayıs don't know about it.
They don't know what is Osman up to.
Let me handle it.
I kept every word of mine.
Enough!
Osman Bey is coming!
My Osman.
Osman!
May Allah protect you, my Bey!
Alps!
Tell us what you saw.
We saw some things.
We have some bad news.
Geyhatu has gathered his army and...
is going to Kayı tribe.
He won't wait.
Geyhatu and his soldiers have
come a long way.
They should drink our cold Ayran and rest.
We offer you our cold Ayran while...
you offer us blood, Geyhatu.
Where is my son, Osman?
The son who doesn't know the ancestors...
don't deserve anything.
When they are in the womb...
they born.
I think you shouldn't call the name...
of your son who isn't appropriate
for your ancestor Genghis Khan.
It's not a good manner, Geyhatu.
Osman...
I'll kill you, Turk!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com